AFL-CIO Railway Employees' Department Records on Microfilm 5478 mf
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- Sub-Series 22: 1922 Strike Files, 1922-1925
  - Series 22: 1922 Strike Files (Reel no.10) (Reel 50)
    - New York Central Lines, 1922-1942; 1 (Reel 50)
      Code no. 3C-31 pt.2: September 20, 1922 - September 25, 1942
    - New York Central Lines, 1922-1923; 2 (Reel 50)
      Code no. 3C-31 extra: September 15, 1922 - February 22, 1923
    - Illinois Central Railroad, 1923-1949; 3 (Reel 50)
      Code no. 3C-32: January 18, 1923 - February 7, 1949
  - Series 22: 1922 Strike Files (Reel no.11) (Reel 51)
    - Illinois Central Railroad, 1922-1923; 1 (Reel 51)
      Code no. 3C-32: June 27, 1922 - January 18, 1923
    - Big Four Railroad, 1922; 2 (Reel 51)
      Code no. 3C-33: July 28, 1922 November 24, 1922
  - Series 22: 1922 Strike Files (Reel no.12) (Reel 52)
    - Big Four Railroad, 1922; 1 (Reel 52)
      Code no. 3C-33 pt.1: June 27, 1922 - July 28, 1922
    - Big Four Railroad, 1922-1942; 2 (Reel 52)
      Code no. 3C-33 pt.2: September 16, 1922 - August 12, 1942
    - Lehigh Valley Railroad, 1922-1923; 3 (Reel 52)
      Code no. 3C-34: June 27, 1922 - November 28, 1923
    - Chicago, Milwaukee and St. Paul Railroad, 1923; 4 (Reel 52)
      Code no. 3C-35: March 1, 1923 - April 12, 1923
  - Series 22: 1922 Strike Files (Reel no.13) (Reel 53)
    - Chicago, Milwaukee and St. Paul Railway, 1922-1923; 1 (Reel 53)
      Code no. 3C-35: June 27, 1922 - February 27, 1923
    - Erie Railroad, 1922-1938; 2 (Reel 53)
      Code no. 3C-36: July 25, 1922 - July 7, 1938
  - Series 22: 1922 Strike Files (Reel no.14) (Reel 54)
    - Erie Railroad, 1922; 1 (Reel 54)
      Code no. 3C-36: June 27, 1922 - July 24, 1922
    - Michigan Central Railroad, 1922-1924; 2 (Reel 54)
      Code no. 3C-37: June 27, 1922 - June 12, 1924
    - Macon, Dublin and Savannah Railroad, 1922; 3 (Reel 54)
      Code no. 3C-38: June 27, 1922 - October 16, 1922
    - Akron, Canton, Youngstown Railroad, 1922; 4 (Reel 54)
      Code no. 3C-39: June 27, 1922 - November 6, 1922
    - Chicago Rock Island Railroad, 1922; 5 (Reel 54)
      Code no. 3C-40 pt.1: August 30, 1922 - December 20, 1922
    - Chicago Rock Island Railroad, 1922; 6 (Reel 54)
      Code no. 3C-40 pt.1: August 11, 1922 - August 30, 1922
  - Series 22: 1922 Strike Files (Reel no.15) (Reel 55)
    - Chicago Rock Island Railroad, 1922-1923; 1 (Reel 55)
      Code no. 3C-40 pt.2: July 31, 1922 - January 3, 1923
    - Chicago Rock Island Railroad, 1924-1940; 2 (Reel 55)
      Code no. 3C-40 pt.3: March 14, 1924 - October 17,1940
  - Series 22: 1922 Strike Files (Reel no.16) (Reel 56)
    - Chicago Rock Island Railroad, 1923-1924; 1 (Reel 56)
      Code no. 3C-40 pt.3: October 29, 1923 - March 13, 1924
    - Pere Marquette Railroad, 1922-1923; 2 (Reel 56)
      Code no. 3C-41: June 27, 1922 - October 17, 1923
    - International and Great Northern Railroad, 1922-1923; 3 (Reel 56)
      Code no. 3C-42: June 27, 1922 - June 13, 1923
  - Series 22: 1922 Strike Files (Reel no.17) (Reel 57)
    - Bessemer and Lake Erie Railroad, 1922-1924; 1 (Reel 57)
      Code no. 3C-43: July 1, 1922 - February 5, 1924
    - Toledo, St. Louis and Western Railroad (commonly known as the Clover Leaf Railroad), 1922-1928; 2 (Reel 57)
      Code no. 3C-44: June 27, 1922 - August 9, 1928
    - Atlanta Great & Sou. Railroad, 1922; 3 (Reel 57)
      Code no. 3C-45: June 27, 1922 - October 6, 1922
    - Atlanta, Tennessee and Great Northern Railroad, 1922-1923; 4 (Reel 57)
      Code no. 3C-46: June 27, 1922 - March 13, 1923
    - Kansas City, Mexico and Orient Railroad, 1922-1923; 5 (Reel 57)
      Code no. 3C-47: June 27, 1922 - October 9, 1923
    - Louisville, Henderson and St. Louis Railroad, 1922-1923; 6 (Reel 57)
      Code no. 3C-48: June 29, 1922 - April 27, 1923
    - Santa Fe Railroad, 1922; 7 (Reel 57)
      Code no. 3C-49 pt.1: October 26, 1922 - October 31, 1922
  - Series 22: 1922 Strike Files (Reel no.18) (Reel 58)
    - Santa Fe Railroad, 1922; 1 (Reel 58)
      Code no. 3C-49 pt.1: June 27, 1922 - October 24, 1922
    - Santa Fe Railroad, 1923; 2 (Reel 58)
      Code no. 3C-49 pt.2: April 14, 1923 - April 28, 1923
  - Series 22: 1922 Strike Files (Reel no.19) (Reel 59)
    - Santa Fe Railroad, 1922-1923; 1 (Reel 59)
      Code no. 3C-49 pt.2: November 1, 1922 - April 28, 1923
    - Santa Fe Railroad, 1923-1924; 2 (Reel 59)
      Code no. 3C-49 pt.3: May 2, 1923 - December 3, 1924
    - Birmingham and Northwestern Railroad, 1922-1923; 3 (Reel 59)
      Code no. 3C-50: July 1, 1922 - October 15, 1923
    - Atlantic Coast Line Railroad, 1923-1931; 4 (Reel 59)
      Code no. 3C-51: November 14, 1923 - January 21, 1931
  - Series 22: 1922 Strike Files (Reel no.20) (Reel 60)
    - Atlantic Coast Line Railroad, 1922-1923; 1 (Reel 60)
      Code no. 3C-51: June 27, 1922 - November 10, 1923
    - Atlanta, Birmingham and Atlantic Railroad, 1921; 2 (Reel 60)
      Code no. 3C-52: April 9, 1921 - August 31, 1921
  - Series 22: 1922 Strike Files (Reel no.21) (Reel 61)
    - Atlanta, Birmingham and Atlantic Railroad, 1920; 1 (Reel 61)
      Code no. 3C-52: December 16, 1920 - April 5, 1921
    - Buffalo, Rochester and Pittsburg Railroad, 1922-1925; 2 (Reel 61)
      Code no. 3C-53: October 9, 1922 - July 29, 1925
  - Series 22: 1922 Strike Files (Reel no.22) (Reel 62)
    - Buffalo, Rochester and Pittsburg Railroad, 1922; 1 (Reel 62)
      Code no. 3C-53: June 27, 1922 - October 9, 1922
    - Boston and Maine Railroad, 1922-1924; 2 (Reel 62)
      Code no. 3C-54: June 27, 1922 - March 26, 1924
    - Buffalo Creek Railroad, 1922-1923; 3 (Reel 62)
      Code no. 3C-55: June 27, 1922 - October 29, 1923
    - Baltimore and Ohio Railroad, 1922; 4 (Reel 62)
      Code no. 3C-56 pt.1: August 2, 1922 - August 17, 1922
  - Series 22: 1922 Strike Files (Reel no.23) (Reel 63)
    - Baltimore and Ohio Railroad, 1922; 1 (Reel 63)
      Code no. 3C-56 pt.1: July 8, 1922 - August 2, 1922
    - Baltimore and Ohio Railroad, 1922; 2 (Reel 63)
      Code no. 3C-56 pt.2: August 19, 1922 - September 13, 1922
  - Series 22: 1922 Strike Files (Reel no.24) (Reel 64)
    - Baltimore and Ohio Railroad, 1922; 1 (Reel 64)
      Code no. 3C-56 pt.2: August 16, 1922 - August 19, 1922
    - Baltimore and Ohio Railroad, 1922-1923; 2 (Reel 64)
      Code no. 3C-56 pt.3: September 12, 1922 - April 24, 1923
    - Chesapeake and Ohio Railroad, 1922-1923; 3 (Reel 64)
      Code no. 3C-57: June 27, 1922 - March 20, 1923
    - Chicago and Eastern Illinois Railroad, 1922-1927; 4 (Reel 64)
      Code no. 3C-58: October 4, 1922 - June 16, 1927
  - Series 22: 1922 Strike Files (Reel no.25) (Reel 65)
    - Chicago and Eastern Illinois Railroad, 1922; 1 (Reel 65)
      Code no. 3C-58: June 27, 1922 - October 3, 1922
    - Chicago and Northwestern Railroad, 1922-1935; 2 (Reel 65)
      Code no. 3C-59: June 27, 1922 - January 11, 1935
    - Central Railroad Company of New Jersey, 1922-1923; 3 (Reel 65)
      Code no. 3C-60: June 27, 1922 - August 25, 1923
    - Chicago, Indianapolis and Louisville Railroad, 1922-1923; 4 (Reel 65)
      Code no. 3C-61: August 19, 1922 - May 12, 1923
  - Series 22: 1922 Strike Files (Reel no.26) (Reel 66)
    - Chicago, Indianapolis and Louisville Railroad, 1922; 1 (Reel 66)
      Code no. 3C-61: June 27, 1922 - August 8, 1922
    - Detroit, Toledo and Ironton Railroad, 1922; 2 (Reel 66)
      Code no. 3C-62: June 27, 1922 - July 1, 1922
    - Lake Erie and Western Railroad, 1922-1923; 3 (Reel 66)
      Code no. 3C-63: June 27, 1922 - September 22, 1923
    - Delaware, Lackawanna and Western Railroad, 1922-1924; 4 (Reel 66)
      Code no. 3C-64 pt.3: June 27, 1922 - September 19, 1924
    - Delaware, Lackawanna and Western Railroad, 1924-1925; 5 (Reel 66)
      Code no. 3C-64 pt.4: June 21, 1924 - February 2, 1925
    - Denver and Rio Grande Railway, 1922-1923; 6 (Reel 66)
      Code no. 3C-65: June 27, 1922 - August 20, 1923
  - Series 22: 1922 Strike Files (Reel no.27) (Reel 67)
    - Hocking Valley Railroad, 1922-1924; 1 (Reel 67)
      Code no. 3C-66: June 27, 1922 - March 11, 1924
    - Davenport, Rock Island and Northwestern Railroad, 1922; 2 (Reel 67)
      Code no. 3C-67: June 30, 1922 - October 21, 1922
    - Gulf Coast Lines and Houston Belt and Terminal Railroad, 1922-1923; 3 (Reel 67)
      Code no. 3C-68: June 27, 1922 - February 23, 1923
    - King Street Terminal Railway, 1922-1923; 4 (Reel 67)
      Code no. 3C-69: June 27, 1922 - April 5, 1923
    - Kansas City Southern Railroad, 1922-1923; 5 (Reel 67)
      Code no. 3C-70: June 27, 1922 - June 9, 1923
    - Kentucky and Indiana Terminal Railroad, 1922-1923; 6 (Reel 67)
      Code no. 3C-71: June 27, 1922 - November 9, 1923
    - Louisiana and Arkansas Railroad, 1922-1932; 7 (Reel 67)
      Code no. 3C-72: June 27, 1922 - January 26, 1932
    - Missouri Pacific Railroad, 1922; 8 (Reel 67)
      Code no. 3C-73 pt.1: December 19, 1922 - December 31, 1922
  - Series 22: 1922 Strike Files (Reel no.28) (Reel 68)
    - Missouri Pacific Railroad, 1922; 1 (Reel 68)
      Code no. 3C-73 pt.1: July 1, 1922 - December 19, 1922
    - Missouri Pacific Railroad, 1923; 2 (Reel 68)
      Code no. 3C-73 pt.2: March 17, 1923 - June 30, 1923
  - Series 22: 1922 Strike Files (Reel no.29) (Reel 69)
    - Missouri Pacific Railroad, 1923; 1 (Reel 69)
      Code no. 3C-73 pt.2: January 2, 1923 - March 16, 1923
    - Missouri Pacific Railroad, 1923-1924; 2 (Reel 69)
      Code no. 3C-73 pt.3: July 3, 1923 - April 3, 1924
    - Missouri Pacific Railroad, 1924-1942; 3 (Reel 69)
      Code no. 3C-73 pt.4: November 21, 1924 - September 25, 1942
  - Series 22: 1922 Strike Files (Reel no.30) (Reel 70)
    - Missouri Pacific Railroad, 1924; 1 (Reel 70)
      Code no. 3C-73 pt.4: April 4, 1924 - November 14, 1924
    - Mobile and Ohio Railroad, 1922-1923; 2 (Reel 70)
      Code no. 3C-74: June 27, 1922 - January 30, 1923
    - Missouri, Kansas and Texas Lines, 1922; 3 (Reel 70)
      Code no. 3C-75 pt.1: July 21, 1922 - December 31, 1922
  - Series 22: 1922 Strike Files (Reel no.31) (Reel 71)
    - Missouri, Kansas and Texas Lines, 1922; 1 (Reel 71)
      Code no. 3C-75 pt.1: June 27, 1922 - July 20, 1922
    - Missouri, Kansas and Texas Lines, 1923-1938; 2 (Reel 71)
      Code no. 3C-75 pt.2: January 4, 1923 - July 7, 1938
    - Norfolk and Western Railroad, 1922-1923; 3 (Reel 71)
      Code no. 3C-76 pt.1: August 28, 1922 - April 21, 1923
  - Series 22: 1922 Strike Files (Reel no.32) (Reel 72)
    - Norfolk and Western Railroad, 1922; 1 (Reel 72)
      Code no. 3C-76: June 27, 1922 - August 8, 1922
    - Norfolk and Western Railroad, 1923-1942; 2 (Reel 72)
      Code no. 3C-76 pt.2: May 5, 1923 - June 18, 1942
    - New York, New Haven and Hartford Railroad, 1922-1923; 3 (Reel 72)
      Code no. 3C-77 pt.1: June 27, 1922 - November 28, 1923
  - Series 22: 1922 Strike Files (Reel no.33) (Reel 73)
    - New York, New Haven and Hartford Railroad, 1923-1939; 1 (Reel 73)
      Code no. 3C-77 pt.2: December 5, 1923 - December 1, 1939
    - Northern Pacific Railroad, 1922-1924; 2 (Reel 73)
      Code no. 3C-78: June 27, 1922 - July 30, 1924
    - Richmond, Fredericksburg and Potomac Railroad, 1922-1923; 3 (Reel 73)
      Code no. 3C-79: June 27, 1922 - August 10, 1923
    - Southern Railroad, 1922-1923; 4 (Reel 73)
      Code no. 3C-80: June 27, 1922 - May 24, 1923
  - Series 22: 1922 Strike Files (Reel no.34) (Reel 74)
    - St. Louis, South Western Railroad, 1922-1923; 1 (Reel 74)
      Code no. 3C-81: June 27, 1922 - October 17, 1923
    - San Antonio Uvalde and Gulf Railroad, 1922-1923; 2 (Reel 74)
      Code no. 3C-82: July 1, 1922 - April 20, 1923
    - Southern Pacific Railroad, 1922; 3 (Reel 74)
      Code no. 3C-83 pt.1: July 16, 1922 - December 30, 1922
  - Series 22: 1922 Strike Files (Reel no.35) (Reel 75)
    - Southern Pacific Railroad, 1922; 1 (Reel 75)
      Code no. 3C-83: June 27, 1922 - July 16, 1922
    - Southern Pacific Railroad, 1923-1938; 2 (Reel 75)
      Code no. 3C-83 pt.2: January 4, 1923 - December 14, 1938
    - St. Louis and San Francisco Railroad, 1922-1923; 3 (Reel 75)
      Code no. 3C-84 pt.1: June 27, 1922 - April 21, 1923
    - St. Louis and San Francisco Railroad, 1923-1935; 4 (Reel 75)
      Code no. 3C-84 pt.2: November 5, 1923 - May 27, 1935
  - Series 22: 1922 Strike Files (Reel no.36) (Reel 76)
    - St. Louis and San Francisco Railroad, 1923; 1 (Reel 76)
      3C-84: May 5, 1923 - November 3, 1923
    - Spokane, Portland and Seattle Railroad, 1922-1923; 2 (Reel 76)
      3C-85: June 27, 1922 - January 25, 1923
    - Trans-Mississippi Terminal Railroad, 1922-1923; 3 (Reel 76)
      3C-86: June 27, 1922 - March 16, 1923
    - Trinity and Brazos Valley Railroad, 1922-1923; 4 (Reel 76)
      3C-87: June 27, 1922 - November 8, 1923
    - Texas and Pacific Railway, 1922-1924; 5 (Reel 76)
      3C-88: June 27, 1922 - April 3, 1924
    - Union Pacific Railroad, 1922; 6 (Reel 76)
      3C-89 pt.1: September 2, 1922 - December 31, 1922
  - Series 22: 1922 Strike Files (Reel no.37) (Reel 77)
    - Union Pacific Railroad, 1922; 1 (Reel 77)
      Code no. 3C-89: June 27, 1922 - September 1, 1922
    - Union Pacific Railroad, 1923-1930; 2 (Reel 77)
      Code no. 3C-89 pt.2: January 1, 1923 - May 9, 1930
    - Virginian Railroad, 1922-1939; 3 (Reel 77)
      Code no. 3C-90: October 7, 1922 - January 8, 1939
  - Series 22: 1922 Strike Files (Reel no.38) (Reel 78)
    - Virginian Railroad, 1922; 1 (Reel 78)
      Code no. 3C-90: June 27, 1922 - October 7, 1922
    - Wheeling and Lake Erie Railroad, 1922-1927; 2 (Reel 78)
      Code no. 3C-91: June 27, 1922 - January 8, 1927
    - Wabash Railroad, 1922-1925; 3 (Reel 78)
      Code no. 3C-92: June 27, 1922 - January 26, 1925
  - Series 22: 1922 Strike Files (Reel no.39) (Reel 79)
    - Atlanta Joint Terminal, 1922-1923; 1 (Reel 79)
      Code no. 3C-93: June 27, 1922 - May 16, 1923
    - Indiana Harbor Belt Railroad, 1922-1923; 2 (Reel 79)
      Code no. 3C-94: July 1, 1922 - December 17, 1923
    - Rock Island Southern Railroad, 1922-1923; 3 (Reel 79)
      Code no. 3C-95: June 27, 1922 - April 3, 1923
    - Colorado, Wyoming and Eastern Railroad, 1922; 4 (Reel 79)
      Code no. 3C-96: June 27, 1922 - October 4, 1922
    - Long Island Railroad, 1922-1924; 5 (Reel 79)
      Code no. 3C-97: June 27, 1922 - June 20, 1924
    - Grand Trunk Railroad, 1922-1923; 6 (Reel 79)
      Code no. 3C-98: June 27, 1922 - January 20, 1923
    - Seaboard Airline Railroad, 1922-1923; 7 (Reel 79)
      Code no. 3C-99: June 27, 1922 - February 27, 1923
    - Kansas City Terminal Railroad, 1922-1925; 8 (Reel 79)
      Code no. 3C-100: June 27, 1922 - January 23, 1925
    - Mississippi Central Railroad, 1922-1923; 9 (Reel 79)
      Code no. 3C-101: June 27, 1922 - March 7, 1923
    - Georgia Railroad, 1922-1931; 10 (Reel 79)
      Code no. 3C-102: June 27, 1922 - October 24, 1931
    - Kansas, Oklahoma & Gulf Railroad, 1922-1923; 11 (Reel 79)
      Code no. 3C-103: July 1, 1922 - April 3, 1923
    - Elgin, Joliet and Eastern Railroad, 1922-1923; 12 (Reel 79)
      Code no. 3C-104: September 8, 1922 - April 30, 1923
  - Series 22: 1922 Strike Files (Reel no.40) (Reel 80)
    - Elgin, Joliet and Eastern Railroad, 1922; 1 (Reel 80)
      Code no. 3C-104: June 27, 1922 - September 7, 1922
    - Public Belt Railroad, 1922-1923; 2 (Reel 80)
      Code no. 3C-105: June 27, 1922 - June 8, 1923
    - Louisiana Railway and Navigation Company Railroad, 1922-1938; 3 (Reel 80)
      Code no. 3C-106: June 27, 1922 - August 10, 1938
    - Bangor and Aroostook Railroad, 1922-1923; 4 (Reel 80)
      Code no. 3C-107: June 24, 1922 - December 11, 1923
    - El Paso and Southern Railroad, 1922-1923; 5 (Reel 80)
      Code no. 3C-108: February 1, 1922 - June 29, 1923
    - Central Vermont Railway, 1922-1923; 6 (Reel 80)
      Code no. 3C-109: June 27, 1922 - February 2, 1923
    - Great Northern Railway, 1922-1923; 7 (Reel 80)
      Code no. 3C-110: September 6, 1922 - February 18, 1923
  - Series 22: 1922 Strike Files (Reel no.41) (Reel 81)
    - Great Northern Railway, 1922; 1 (Reel 81)
      Code no. 3C-110: June 27, 1922 - September 5, 1922
    - Unidentified, 1922; 2 (Reel 81)
      Code no. 3C-111: June 27, 1922 - July 5, 1922
    - Pullman Railroad, 1922-1924; 3 (Reel 81)
      Code no. 3C-112: June 27, 1922 - June 7, 1924
    - Missouri and Illinois Railroad, 1922-1923; 4 (Reel 81)
      Code no. 3C-113: June 27, 1922 - April 10, 1923
    - Western Maryland Railroad, 1941; 5 (Reel 81)
      Code no. 3C-114: March 4, 1941 - March 7, 1941
    - Wabash, Chester and Western Railroad, 1922-1923; 6 (Reel 81)
      Code no. 3C-115: June 27, 1922 - April 25, 1923
    - Northwestern Pacific Railroad, 1922-1923; 7 (Reel 81)
      Code no. 3C-116: July 6, 1922 - March 15, 1923
    - Buffalo and Susquehanna Railroad, 1922-1923; 8 (Reel 81)
      Code no. 3C-117: July 4, 1922 - June 13, 1923
    - Utah Railway, 1922; 9 (Reel 81)
      Code no. 3C-118: June 27, 1922 - December 18, 1922
    - Duluth and Iron Range Railway, 1922-1923; 10 (Reel 81)
      Code no. 3C-119: June 27, 1922 - April 3, 1923
    - Duluth, Missabe and Northern Railway, 1922-1923; 11 (Reel 81)
      Code no. 3C-120: June 27, 1922 - April 3, 1923
    - Cumberland and Pennsylvania Railroad, 1922; 12 (Reel 81)
      Code no. 3C-121: June 27, 1922 - October 11, 1922
    - Chicago and Alton Railroad, 1923-1938; 13 (Reel 81)
      Code no. 3C-122: January 15, 1923 - July 5, 1938
  - Series 22: 1922 Strike Files (Reel no.42) (Reel 82)
    - Chicago and Alton Railroad, 1922-1923; 1 (Reel 82)
      Code no. 3C-122: June 27, 1922 - January 2, 1923
    - Illinois Northern Railroad, 1922-1923; 2 (Reel 82)
      Code no. 3C-123: June 27, 1922 - March 14, 1923
    - Wichita and Southern Railroad, 1922; 3 (Reel 82)
      Code no. 3C-124: June 27, 1922 - July 17, 1922
    - Minneapolis and St. Louis Railroad, 1921-1923; 4 (Reel 82)
      Code no. 3C-125: May 26, 1921 - May 17, 1923
    - Chicago Great Western Railroad, 1922-1923; 5 (Reel 82)
      Code no. 3C-126: June 27, 1922 - April 12, 1923
    - Pittsburg and Shawmut Railroad, 1922-1923; 6 (Reel 82)
      Code no. 3C-127: June 27, 1922 - July 6, 1923
    - Washington Terminal Railroad, 1922-1923; 7 (Reel 82)
      Code no. 3C-128: June 27, 1922 - November 10, 1923
    - Florida East Coast Railroad, 1922-1923; 8 (Reel 82)
      Code no. 3C-129: October 24, 1922 - October 11, 1923
  - Series 22: 1922 Strike Files (Reel no.43) (Reel 83)
    - Florida East Coast Railroad, 1922; 1 (Reel 83)
      Code no. 3C-129: June 23, 1922 - October 19, 1922
    - Georgia, Southern and Florida Railway, 1922; 2 (Reel 83)
      Code no. 3C-130: June 27, 1922 - October 12, 1922
    - General Strike File, 1923-1925; 3 (Reel 83)
      Code no. 3C-131-General Daugherty Injunction. June 30, 1923 - April 29, 1925
    - General Strike File, 1923-1925; 4 (Reel 83)
      Code no. 3C-131-General: March 1, 1923 - January26, 1925
    - General Strike File, 1928-1952; 5 (Reel 83)
      Code no. 3C-131-General: March 4, 1928 - January 22, 1952
  - Series 22: 1922 Strike Files (Reel no.44) (Reel 84)
    - General Strike File, 1925-1928; 1 (Reel 84)
      Code no. 3C-131: April 13, 1925 - March 8, 1928
    - Strike File. St. Paul Railroad Injunction, 1923; 2 (Reel 84)
      Code no. 3C-131: April 26, 1923 - October 31, 1923
    - Strike File. Maine Central Railroad, 1922-1924; 3 (Reel 84)
      Code no. 3C-131: June 27, 1922 - January 23, 1924
    - Strike Files. Proposed Conferences of Governors, 1923; 4 (Reel 84)
      Code no. 3C-131: Governors on 1922 Strike. March 12, 1923 - July 12, 1923
    - Extra Copies of 1922 Strike Ballot, 5 (Reel 84)
      Code no. 3C-131: June 8, 1922
    - Duluth, Winnipeg and Pacific Railroad, 1922; 6 (Reel 84)
      Code no. 3C-132: June 27, 1922 - October 21, 1922
    - Jacksonville Terminal Railroad, 1922-1925; 7 (Reel 84)
      Code no. 3C-133: June 27, 1922 - March 22, 1924
    - Charleston and Western Carolina Railroad, 1922-1923; 8 (Reel 84)
      Code no. 3C-134: June 27, 1922 - June 27, 1923
    - Columbus and Greenville Railroad, 1922-1923; 9 (Reel 84)
      Code no. 3C-135: July 3, 1922 - May 15, 1923
    - Western Pacific Railroad, 1922-1923; 10 (Reel 84)
      Code no. 3C-136: July 5, 1922 - December 20, 1923
    - Chicago Junction Railroad, 1922-1923; 11 (Reel 84)
      Code no. 3C-137: July 10, 1922 - November 30, 1923
    - Butte, Anaconda and Pacific Railroad, 1922-1923; 12 (Reel 84)
      Code no. 3C-138: June 29, 1922 - March 14, 1923
    - Colorado and Southern Railroad, 1923; 13 (Reel 84)
      Code no. 3C-139: March 6, 1923 - October 23, 1923
  - Series 22: 1922 Strike Files (Reel no.45) (Reel 85)
    - Colorado and Southern Railroad, 1922-1923; 1 (Reel 85)
      Code no. 3C-139: July 2, 1922 - February 18, 1923
    - Des Moines Railroad, 1922-1923; 2 (Reel 85)
      Code no. 3C-140: June 27, 1922 - January 6, 1923
    - American Locomotive Works Company, 1922; 3 (Reel 85)
      Code no. 3C-141: July 6, 1922 - December 19, 1922
    - Kanawha and Michigan Railroad, 1922-1923; 4 (Reel 85)
      Code no. 3C-142: July 11, 1922 - March 10, 1923
    - Atlanta and West Point Railroad, 1922-1923; 5 (Reel 85)
      Code no. 3C-143: July 10, 1922 - May 7, 1923
    - Ft. Smith and Western Railroad, 1922; 6 (Reel 85)
      Code no. 3C-144: July 8, 1922 - October 17, 1922
    - Chicago, St. Paul and Minneapolis and Omaha Railway Co. vs. Michaelson, et. al., 1922-1930; 7 (Reel 85)
      Code no. 3C-145: September 4, 1930 - July 5, 1922
  - Series 22: 1922 Strike Files (Reel no.46) (Reel 86)
    - Norfolk Southern Railroad, 1922-1923; 1 (Reel 86)
      Code no. 3C-146: July 10, 1922 - October 23, 1923
    - Lehigh and Hudson River Railroad, 1922-1923; 2 (Reel 86)
      Code no. 3C-147: July 10, 1922 - March 14, 1923
    - Texas City Terminal Railroad, 1922-1923; 3 (Reel 86)
      Code no. 3C-148: July 11, 1922 - November 13, 1923
    - Texas Midland Railroad, 1922-1923; 4 (Reel 86)
      Code no. 3C-149: July 8, 1922 - January 31, 1923
    - Hudson and Manhattan Railroad, 1922-1923; 5 (Reel 86)
      Code no. 3C-150: July 6, 1922 - March 14, 1923
    - H&TC (part of Southern Pacific Railroad), 1922-1923; 6 (Reel 86)
      Code no. 3C-151: July 18, 1922 - April 5, 1923
    - Chicago, Peoria and St. Louis Railroad, 1922-1923; 7 (Reel 86)
      Code no. 3C-152: July 14, 1922 - May 1, 1923
    - American Refrigerator Transit Company, 1922-1924; 8 (Reel 86)
      Code no. 3C-153: July 13, 1922 - November 5, 1924
    - Central of Georgia Railroad, 1922-1923; 9 (Reel 86)
      Code no. 3C-154: July 11, 1922 - December 5, 1923
    - Fort Worth and Denver City Railroad, 1922-1923; 10 (Reel 86)
      Code no. 3C-155: July 16, 1922 - December 27, 1923
    - Soo Line Railroad, 1922-1923; 11 (Reel 86)
      Code no. 3C-156: July 15, 1922 - February 27, 1923
    - Vicksburg, Shreveport and Pacific Railroad, 1922-1923; 12 (Reel 86)
      Code no. 3C-157: July 17, 1922 - May 31, 1923
    - Marion and Eastern Railroad, 1922; 13 (Reel 86)
      Code no. 3C-158: July 14, 1922 - August 25, 1922
    - Wichita Falls and Northwestern Railroad, 1922-1923; 14 (Reel 86)
      Code no. 3C-159: July 18, 1922 - March 27, 1923
    - Nevada, California and Oregon Railroad, 1922-1923; 15 (Reel 86)
      Code no. 3C-160: June 29, 1922 - June 16, 1923
    - Columbia, Newberry & Laurens Railroad, 1922-1923; 16 (Reel 86)
      Code no. 3C-161: June 30, 1922 - December 5, 1923
    - Fort Worth and Belt Railroad, 1922; 17 (Reel 86)
      Code no. 3C-162: August 3, 1922 -October 11, 1922
    - Oklahoma, New Mexico and Pacific Railroad, 1922-1923; 18 (Reel 86)
      Code no. 3C-163: August 5, 1922 - July 25, 1923
    - East St. Louis Railway, 1922; 19 (Reel 86)
      Code no. 3C-164: August 5, 1922
  - Series 22: 1922 Strike Files (Reel no.47) (Reel 87)